thank you hello everyone today I am
harvesting some wild flowers from a
variety of wild shrubs growing on my
property
many of these bushes are not often found
in urban areas due to their petals often
being released quite quickly some bushes
grow berries that fall and cause sticky
residue on sidewalks many of these
species are considered therefore rather
messy but I like them and I especially
like to see them growing in Wild places
where they don't need to be tidy or
perfect but can instead Thrive Untamed
for me they symbolize the strength that
comes from building a deep root system
that can find water and nutrients to
support life even when times are hard
I still experience uncomfortable
emotions but I've improved on accepting
things as they are messy and otherwise
I make videos for the most part when I'm
feeling positive and cheerful but I
don't always feel that way while I share
with you the things I love about life
here there's a lot of imperfection as
well I've had some experiences in my
younger years that left me feeling
deeply lost with low self-esteem life
certainly felt messy back then fast
forward to today things are much better
and completely different but now there
are new questions questions about my
career and what I want to do next year
my siblings now live far away one on the
other side of the planet and I miss them
dearly in terms of relationships with
others and personal challenges
everything is wonderfully imperfect but
also perpetually evolving towards
something new something better though
not always easier and perhaps it should
be that way if everything was easy I'd
have no reason to grow like the wild
shrubs on my property it is only harsh
conditions that make their Roots Venture
deeper into the soil to find something
to help them withstand the storms
foreign
teach us what to Value overwhelming
experiences teaches the importance of
growth mistakes can lead to experience
self-criticism to wisdom emotional
overwhelm to emotional intelligence fear
to spirituality
much of what seems negative can also
bring about great healing and strength
thank you
[Music]
foreign
I started moving forward when I accepted
that what had happened so far in my life
is simply what had happened yes perhaps
some of it was unfair some was painful
especially the experiences that leave
invisible scars but it happened and all
that is left for me to do is wonder
where do I go from here
I had to stop giving power to those who
brought me pain and instead give that
power to myself and appreciate how far
I've come
foreign
to paraphrase Christopher Robin what if
you are actually stronger than you seem
braver than you believe smarter than you
think who would you be who is that
person
things are messy sometimes and unfair
and complicated there will always be
someone out there that is something I
wish I had or is better at something
than me or seems to be more put together
but I'm trying not to hold regret and
self-criticism in my heart because so
far in my life it has never served me
now every morning I ask myself where
will I go from here and that question is
starting to feel more and more exciting
foreign
you find me out here next to my bed of
bleeding hearts and Sweet William I'm so
happy that they're doing so well they
were just these tiny little Sprouts last
year and this year they're like three
four feet tall so it is amazing and I'm
just so happy with them how well they've
been growing it is interesting how when
it comes to plants if you find just the
right spot for them to be with just
enough Sun just enough water and
moisture they Thrive and they bloom I
often think of that in regards to
ourselves that often small adjustments
in our own lives can make such a big
difference at this moment I'm not quite
sure what I'm going to title this video
but one thing that is coming to mind at
the moment is how important it is for me
to appreciate and accept all the more
complicated or Messier times in life
when things are not going as the core
according to dreamed or planned it
really is because of those challenging
times that you do appreciate the good
and I know that is hard to accept in the
moment but for me it's always been true
it's because I have known what it's like
to be at Rock Bottom at least for me I
really can truly appreciate right now
feeling so peaceful and grounded in this
new phase of my life where I am really
tackling challenges head on and not
trying to run away from emotions and
memories anymore one thing that comes to
mind is the example of my own mother she
grew up in poverty and her mother grew
up in a very horrible unsafe living
situation and had a very difficult
childhood
for my own mother she used to tell me
the story of how she would find old
copies of readers digests and cut out
the photos in the back that tended to be
landscape paintings and photos she would
paste them on the door of her bedroom
and when she was feeling anxious or
stressed or overwhelmed due to the very
difficult life situation she was in she
would spend time looking at those images
and letting their warmth and that beauty
of nature to warm her and Inspire her to
keep going and to keep looking for the
positive and the light in these videos I
love to focus on things that make me
happy and make me feel positive but of
course there are so many messy things
that happen in my own life and and
everyone's but I do like to use this
channel as an outlet for things that
help me continue to feel renewed and
find Joy speaking of I'm going to be
making a video soon talking about you
YouTube and changes and what's going to
be happening I think it's going to be a
very big video and I'm going to share a
lot so stay tuned for that because I've
been meaning to make it for quite a
while
so you can expect that video in a month
or so and in the meantime I really
should get out of the rain because it is
starting to really pour down so
um all right I guess uh I guess the
skies are telling me it's time to wrap
this up I'm sending you so much love I
do have a special thing happening on my
Etsy shop this week it is just an idea I
got that is brand new I don't think I've
done anything like this before I'm going
to be selling mystery letters with some
poems and other little scrapbooking
materials inside along with a bundle of
my very favorite art pieces and so it's
going to be a handwritten note and when
you order it you can write along with
your order some comments or questions
you would like me to address in the note
it will be a sort of fairy male and it
is kind of a test run so I only have
about two dozen or so envelopes but I
wanted to let you know I'm excited to
put together some really special letters
for some of you so I'm sending you all
my love and I will see you very very
soon goodbye